universities.com 2019-04-07

# Universities.com Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Universities.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.universities.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Universities.com.

* * *

### Personal identification information ("PII")

We may collect personal identification information ("PII") from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. PII that may be collected includes information such as your first name, last name, date of birth, telephone number, mailing and home address, zip code, or e-mail address (collectively referred to herein as "PII"). Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously but may have limited access to certain sections or information on the site. We will collect PII from users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. 

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

### How we use collect and use your Personal identification information ("PII")

When Placing an Order, we may use the PII users provide about themselves when placing an order to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.�The email address users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If a user decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the user would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or user may contact us via our Site.

When Requesting Information on Universities.com, you agree that we may share such PII with Third Party Providers in order to complete your request for specific products and/or services that you applied for from such Third-Party Providers, and that they may use such personal information for any lawful purposes, subject to any restrictions contained herein. Any information that you supply to Universities.com may be shared with a third-party marketing company for the purpose of email marketing, telemarketing, SMS marketing, or postal direct marketing. Any information that you supply to any Third-Party Providers shall be governed by the applicable Third Party Providers� privacy policy.

If you provide your express consent to receive telemarketing calls, Universities.com may use your PII (including any information which may reasonably be derived therefrom) to contact you, directly or indirectly, using the telephone number provided, in order to facilitate your request regarding the products and/or services which you requested information for or products and/or services you may be interested.

### Payment Data

If you sign up to purchase any of our Paid Subscriptions (as defined in the�Terms & Conditions), your credit or debit card information (such as card type and expiration date) and other financial data that we need to process your payment may be collected and stored by the payment processors with which we work. We may also collect some limited information, such as your postal code, mobile number, and details of your transaction history, all of which are necessary to provide the Service. In addition, the payment processors generally provide us with some limited information related to you, such as a unique token that enables you to make additional purchases using the information they�ve stored, and your card�s type, expiration date, and certain digits of your card number. 

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

### Children�s Privacy

Protecting children's privacy is important to us. We do not direct the Site to, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from, children under the age of thirteen. 

### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

### Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non-personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

### Changes to this privacy policy

Universities.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, your dealings with this site, or to opt-out of our services please contact us at: 

Prospex Digital, LLC (DBA Universities.com)  
280 Hwy 35, Suite 100, Red Bank, NJ 07701  
732-784-4347

https://www.universities.com  
info@universities.com

This document was last updated on April 27, 2018.
